(this["webpackJsonpsorting-hat"]=this["webpackJsonpsorting-hat"]||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(17)},16:function(e,t,n){},17:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var s=n(6),a=n(9),r=n(1),o=n(2),i=n(4),l=n(3),u=n(7),c=n(5),h=n(0),p=n.n(h),f=n(10),d=n.n(f),y=function(e){function t(){return Object(r.a)(this,t),Object(i.a)(this,Object(l.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(c.a)(t,e),Object(o.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return p.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-option"},p.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",className:"radioCustomButton",name:"radioGroup",checked:this.props.answerType===this.props.answer,id:this.props.answerType,value:this.props.answerType,disabled:this.props.answer,onChange:this.props.onAnswerSelected}),p.a.createElement("label",{className:"radioCustomLabel",htmlFor:this.props.answerType},this.props.answerContent))}}]),t}(p.a.Component),w=function(e){function t(){return Object(r.a)(this,t),Object(i.a)(this,Object(l.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(c.a)(t,e),Object(o.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return p.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-container"},p.a.createElement("h3",{className:"question"},this.props.content))}}]),t}(p.a.Component);n(16);var m=function(e){return p.a.createElement("div",{className:"quiz-container",key:e.questionId},p.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-and-answers"},p.a.createElement(w,{content:e.question}),p.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-options-container"},e.answerOptions.map((function(t){return p.a.createElement(y,{key:t.content,answerContent:t.content,answerType:t.type,answer:e.answer,questionId:e.questionId,onAnswerSelected:e.onAnswerSelected})})))))},v=function(e){function t(){return Object(r.a)(this,t),Object(i.a)(this,Object(l.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(c.a)(t,e),Object(o.a)(t,[{key:"showHouseColor",value:function(){return"Gryffindor"===this.props.result?"gryffindor":"Hufflepuff"===this.props.result?"hufflepuff":"Slytherin"===this.props.result?"slytherin":"Ravenclaw"===this.props.result?"ravenclaw":void 0}},{key:"render",value:function(){return p.a.createElement("div",{className:"quiz-container"},p.a.createElement("div",{className:"results-container ".concat(this.showHouseColor())},p.a.createElement("h2",{className:"title"},this.props.result),"Gryffindor"===this.props.result&&p.a.createElement("div",null,p.a.createElement("div",{className:"house-crest gryffindor-crest"}),p.a.createElement("p",{className:"house-description gryffindor-description"},"Gryffindor values courage, bravery, nerve, and chivalry.")),"Hufflepuff"===this.props.result&&p.a.createElement("div",null,p.a.createElement("div",{className:"house-crest hufflepuff-crest"}),p.a.createElement("p",{className:"house-description hufflepuff-description"},"Hufflepuff values hard work, patience, justice, and loyalty.")),"Ravenclaw"===this.props.result&&p.a.createElement("div",null,p.a.createElement("div",{className:"house-crest ravenclaw-crest"}),p.a.createElement("p",{className:"house-description ravenclaw-description"},"Ravenclaw values intelligence, creativity, learning, and wit.")),"Slytherin"===this.props.result&&p.a.createElement("div",null,p.a.createElement("div",{className:"house-crest slytherin-crest"}),p.a.createElement("p",{className:"house-description slytherin-description "},"Slytherin values ambition, cunning, leadership, and resourcefulness."))))}}]),t}(p.a.Component),g=[{question:"Given the choice, would you rather invent a potion that would guarantee you:",answers:[{type:"Gryffindor",content:"Glory"},{type:"Ravenclaw",content:"Wisdom"},{type:"Hufflepuff",content:"Love"},{type:"Slytherin",content:"Power"}]},{question:"Which road tempts you most?",answers:[{type:"Slytherin",content:"The twisting, leaf-strewn path through woods"},{type:"Hufflepuff",content:"The wide, sunny, grassy lane"},{type:"Ravenclaw",content:"The cobbled street lined with ancient buildings"},{type:"Gryffindor",content:"The narrow, dark, lantern-lit alley"}]},{question:"You enter an enchanted garden. What would you be most curious to examine first?",answers:[{type:"Hufflepuff",content:"The fat red toadstools that appear to be talking to each other"},{type:"Slytherin",content:"The silver leafed tree bearing golden apples"},{type:"Gryffindor",content:"The bubbling pool, in the depths of which something luminous is swirling"},{type:"Ravenclaw",content:"The statue of an old wizard with a strangely twinkling eye"}]},{question:"Once every century, the Flutterby bush produces flowers that adapt their scent to attract the unwary. If it lured you, it would smell of:",answers:[{type:"Ravenclaw",content:"Fresh parchment"},{type:"Gryffindor",content:"A crackling log fire"},{type:"Hufflepuff",content:"Home"},{type:"Slytherin",content:"The Sea"}]},{question:"You and two friends need to cross a bridge guarded by a river troll who insists on fighting one of you before he will let all of you pass. Do you:",answers:[{type:"Slytherin",content:"Suggest that all three of you should fight (without telling the troll."},{type:"Ravenclaw",content:"Suggest drawing lots to decide which of you will fight."},{type:"Hufflepuff",content:"Attempt to confuse the troll into letting all three of you pass without fighting."},{type:"Gryffindor",content:"Volunteer to fight."}]},{question:"After you have died, what would you most like people to do when they hear your name?",answers:[{type:"Hufflepuff",content:"Miss you, but smile"},{type:"Ravenclaw",content:"Ask for more stories about your adventures."},{type:"Gryffindor",content:"Think with admiration of you achievements."},{type:"Slytherin",content:"I don't care what people think of me after I'm dead; it's what they think of me while I'm alive that counts."}]},{question:"Dawn or Dusk?",answers:[{type:"Gryffindor",content:"Dawn"},{type:"Ravenclaw",content:"Dusk"}]},{question:"Black or White?",answers:[{type:"Slytherin",content:"Black"},{type:"Hufflepuff",content:"White"}]},{question:"Forest or River?",answers:[{type:"Slytherin",content:"Forest"},{type:"Ravenclaw",content:"River"}]},{question:"Moon or Stars?",answers:[{type:"Hufflepuff",content:"Moon"},{type:"Gryffindor",content:"Stars"}]}],b=function(e){function t(e){var n;return Object(r.a)(this,t),(n=Object(i.a)(this,Object(l.a)(t).call(this,e))).state={counter:0,questionId:1,question:"",answerOptions:[],answer:"",answersCount:{Gryffindor:0,Slytherin:0,Ravenclaw:0,Hufflepuff:0},result:""},n.handleAnswerSelected=n.handleAnswerSelected.bind(Object(u.a)(n)),n}return Object(c.a)(t,e),Object(o.a)(t,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){var e=g.map((function(e){return e.answers}));this.setState({question:g[0].question,answerOptions:e[0]})}},{key:"handleAnswerSelected",value:function(e){var t=this;this.setUserAnswer(e.currentTarget.value),this.state.questionId<g.length?setTimeout((function(){return t.setNextQuestion()}),300):setTimeout((function(){return t.setResults(t.getResults())}),500)}},{key:"setUserAnswer",value:function(e){this.setState((function(t){return{answersCount:Object(a.a)({},t.answersCount,Object(s.a)({},e,(t.answersCount[e]||0)+1)),answer:e}}))}},{key:"setNextQuestion",value:function(){var e=this.state.counter+1,t=this.state.questionId+1;this.setState({counter:e,questionId:t,question:g[e].question,answerOptions:g[e].answers,answer:""})}},{key:"getResults",value:function(){var e=this.state.answersCount,t=Object.keys(e),n=t.map((function(t){return e[t]})),s=Math.max.apply(null,n);return t.filter((function(t){return e[t]===s}))}},{key:"setResults",value:function(e){1===e.length?this.setState({result:e[0]}):this.setState({result:e[Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length)]})}},{key:"render",value:function(){return p.a.createElement("div",null,this.state.result?p.a.createElement(v,{result:this.state.result}):p.a.createElement(m,{answer:this.state.answer,answerOptions:this.state.answerOptions,questionId:this.state.questionId,question:this.state.question,questionTotal:g.length,onAnswerSelected:this.handleAnswerSelected}))}}]),t}(p.a.Component);t.default=b;d.a.render(p.a.createElement(b,null),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[11,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.aed0ec0a.chunk.js.map